<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Things to Fix on A&#43; Accessibility and Inclusive Design Audit</title>
    <link>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Things to Fix on A&#43; Accessibility and Inclusive Design Audit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Form Controls</title>
      <link>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/form-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/form-controls/</guid>
      <description>As a web application, A+ depends on forms to take user input for a range of purposes. The following forms were examined in the tests carried out:
 Log in (local users) Edit profile Create a group Submit an exercise requiring textual input Submit an exercise requiring a file upload  Requirements The following relevant requirements from WCAG were examined:
   1.1.1 Non-text Content (level A):      1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link Purpose</title>
      <link>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/link-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/link-purpose/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Sometimes, assistive technology users will look at a list of links or headings from a web page. VoiceOver allows users to do this from the &amp;ldquo;rotor&amp;rdquo; while browsing the web.
   2.4.4 Link Purpose (In Context) (level A):      2.4.9 Link Purpose (Link Only) (level AAA):    By ensuring the text is descriptive and unique, we enable users to quickly find what they are looking for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links and Buttons</title>
      <link>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/links-and-buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/links-and-buttons/</guid>
      <description>Requirements One key requirement is that names, roles and values can be determined programmatically. The roles are most often deduced from HTML elements (so, for example, a &amp;lt;button&amp;gt; tag can safely be assumed to be a &amp;ldquo;button&amp;rdquo;).
   4.1.2 Name, Role, Value (level A):    In several places, A+ used buttons and links in a different way to the expectation.
Users typically expect that clicking a link takes the user to another page, and clicking a button performs an action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modal Dialogs</title>
      <link>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/modals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/modals/</guid>
      <description>The interface makes heavy use of modal dialogs, for example when a user submits an exercise, the grader results appear in a modal window and when a user views a previous submission, it opens in one. Sometimes, links from modals trigger other modals to open.
Presently, these are not navigable to keyboard users and break the logical focus order. This causes failures in:
   1.3.2 Meaningful Sequence (level A):      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Page Titles</title>
      <link>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/page-titles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/page-titles/</guid>
      <description>Requirements The requirements relating to the page titles are being met. All tested pages have descriptive, discernable names, with the most specific information first and the website name last.
   2.4.1 Bypass Blocks (level A):    Possible Improvements Through testing, it became clear that the use of the | (pipe) character as a divider is annoying when using VoiceOver. Page titles are spoken as:
 Results vertical line programming 2 vertical line a plus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Markup and Sequences</title>
      <link>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/semantic-markup-and-sequences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apluslms.github.io/accessibility-audit/patterns/fixable-a/semantic-markup-and-sequences/</guid>
      <description>Semantic markup When users of screen readers navigate pages, some may rely on the structure of the document to move around. This may mean taking an &amp;ldquo;outline&amp;rdquo;, made up of the nested headings, or using landmarks, such as nav and main to jump around the web page.
Luckily, these often don&amp;rsquo;t need defining explicitly, as many native HTML5 elements have an implied role. In some places, these could be easily swapped into the layout.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>